The Chamber

1. About
2. How to Play
3. Known Bugs
4. Misc 
5. Licenses
6. About the Author

#############################################

1. About
--------

The Chamber started as a small project, just for fun.
Later, it was developed to enter the Pirate Kart V.
It contains some bugs and is not very powerfull, as it
was developed in Free Pascal without any external libraries.

A level editor is also provided which you can download from
http://dl.dropbox.com/u/13615166/Chamber_Editor.rar

2. How to Play
--------------

The game consists in a set of levels. The objective in each level
is to reach the exit (☼) without losing all 3 lives. If you fail,
you return to the Main Menu, but you are able to continue from
the last checkpoint (if you have already reached one). There are
checkpoints every 5 levels.
When completing leves, try to collect goods scattered all around them.
The give a lot of points.

Controls:
- Move using arrows
- Jump pressing Space Bar

3. Known Bugs
-------------

- Users can't press 2 keys simultaniously, due to the standard
keyboard input.

- If you have visual problems, do the following:
	1. Right click at the control bar;
	2. Click 'Properties'
	3. Go to 3rd tab
	4. Change the 'Screen internal memory size' to
		Width: 80
		Height: 300
	5. Change the 'Window size' to
		Width: 80
		Height: 25
	(Optional) 6. Go to the second tab and change de size to '10x20'

4. Misc
-------

Press M in-game to mute or un-mute.

Press ENTER to pause game.

Press ESC at (almost) any time to exit the game. Be aware that
this will not save your progress.

Due to the keyboard bug, the game was coded to offer a smooth input
resulting in being impossible to stop the character when a key is released.
To stop the character, press the UP or DOWN arrow.

The score system adds:
	- 3 points for each life at the end of each level
	- 5 points for each good at the end of each level

5. Licenses
-----------

You are free to distribute this game for FREE, giving credits
to the author.

6. About the Author
-------------------

Rafael Caetano (rafaelvcaetano@hotmail.com)
Twitter: @MAGNUM_PT